- A top guy?
- Yes.
Listen what a nice thing it was now when you cut yourself.
Was on time.
Sorry!
- huh?
Now we are starting to approach shoe and key service.
I think he is.
Oh!
It says on the sign.
Bagarmossen's own De Niro fixes everything.
Hello!
There we have him!
Bagarmossens Robert De Niro.
Rappido, Ey!
Rappido!
You can easily add money to the app by bank card, Apple Pay or bank transfer.
And when you then spend money in the app, you get cashbacks at brands like Nike and Gymshark.
Andale, Andale, Andale!
One of Revolut's absolute most delicious features is how easy it is to spend money abroad with their incredible exchange rates.
You can switch money in the app, or you automatically change your money to the correct currency when using the card.
It couldn't have been easier.
Ay Caramba!
Carajo!
With Revolut you also get access to a walking card that you use at one time online.
When you pay, it disappears and is replaced with a new one.
- Hello!
- Here we have Emmys who in 2019 went viral with this clip.
Which got half the world to believe that Greta Thunberg was lying on a shooting range.
- How many saw that video?
- Any number.
I don't know how many millions of views it has.
It was first spread in Brazil, then it got well attached to the rest of the world in the area against people woke up that day.
- So it was like millions in one day?
- Yes.
- But how similar are you Greta as a person?
- So I like to play computer games, ride a motorcycle.
- What do you play for computer games?
Oh oh oh!
A cod!
YES!
- We got a cod.
- I would probably say that our interests probably differ.
I don't know what she does about the days, but I like firearms.
- Pang, pang?
- Yes Pang Pang.
The best there is.
- Jesus!
Fuck!
- Oh, shit!
–Up, up, up!
- Oh oh oh!
- God, now comes security personnel.
I can't be there anymore.
Oh!
Sorry.
It's like ...
- Yes, but it was well summarized.
It's like what you need to know about me.
- But how similar is Emmy really Greta appearance?
To test it I wanted to see if we could create a viral cliff-
-It pretended that Greta has started sniffing loose.
A strange yet credible news that could act as a test.
Will people see the difference between them?
- You have to change.
I have to buy loose nus.
- Yes.
- This is a real fur.
You absolutely cannot wear it.
A small scarf, just because that effect is so extreme.
There he is!
Yes, that's him!
Come out!
Hello!
My name is Mustiga Mauri.
I am 17 years old, I go to high school-
-and I'm 175 cm tall.
- Hello
- How's it going?
- It is good!
Do you imitate me?
- Nice.
- It was awesome.
- It was the weakest segment on assignment food through before.
- Before the next visit, I thought we would look at some of the tips you emailed but that did not join the clip.
How about the girl who realized that as a child she was very similar to Ola Conny?
Or this woman who is a huge Camilla Läckberg?
And so this incredible GW locomotive bale which unfortunately was unable to record.
This woman is still like Carola.
And so this girl who is sick like in the middle of nature, the program manager, in a very exciting way.
And so my personal favorite, the guy who is not really really like Calle Morreus.
And that was it, now time for the number five list.
And now we will meet Enskedes Anders Bagge who apparently works down there.
And this is where he should be.
Hey!
Hello!
There we have him.
Hi, my name is Anders Bagge.
I have had a construction company here in Enskede for twelve years.
And yes, I'm Anders Bagge.
- It's also the same beard.
- I've had it for 20 years.
- Was it Bagge that turned off you?
- I think so.
- That damn ...
From profile here.
From here it is Anders Bagge.
Here it is ... it is still very much Anders Bagge.
How often do you hear that you ...
- Very often.
- Is this snuff?
- I sniff a lot.
- Now real Bagge will be a newspaper on me when I have such big boxes.
- This is what you call a box too.
That you have it in the back pocket.
Yes, you think it's yummy, huh?
- It is the best.
Do you want a snuff?
Now you have to try a real snuff.
If you dare.
Are you ready?
- No.
- Shall we drive?
- Yes.
- Okay, one, two, three.
- Hey Hey.
You are like, after all.
You have no filter or anything.
That's you.
- No, I'll show that I have no filter.
- Now you are even more similar from this angle.
- Haha, yes thank you.
It's fun to hear that I could be helpful.
- It was incredibly fun to talk to Tjörn Leonardo DiCaprio.
- It was incredibly nice to talk to Mauri aka Ed Sheeran on stilts.
- Haha okay.
Thanks.
And now it's time for the list number three.
- And now we will meet a girl who is very similar, one of Sweden's largest international actors.
And then you get really sad.
Now I'm a douche that dumps you.
Are you ready?
You ... I want to end, I thought.
- So, you're sure?
- Yes, I wanted to end you.
PGA has infidelity, which I have been doing.
- You've been in infidelity.
- Yes.
- Okay, so it's just from nowhere?
- mm.
- Why?
- infidelity.
- huh?
- mm.
- Who?
- Rather which.
- Who is she then?
- Ah?
No...
- Thanks for meeting you.
- Thanks for coming.
- It's damn sick how similar you are.
- A final time.
Now it is time for both number one and two on the list, as we will soon reconcile them as a duo.
- Now it will be about Claes Eriksson from Leif & Billy.
He has an absolutely incredible lookalike, we suspect, far down in southern Sweden.
Today I have attracted him from Blekinge to Stockholm, because we two have big plans.
You are joking!
- Hey!
- And the best thing about you is that you are quite similar, Alfred.
But you are also similar in a different way.
- We were born and raised in the same city, both in Vimmerby.
- Yes.
- We discovered both theater through the same theater association in Vimmerby.
- And then we both have trained as actors at Kalle Flygare here in Stockholm.
- And there they are.
The real ni.
- Because here they play their show today.
And of course we should go in and meet your original.
- Lol!
Hello!
- Do you recognize them?
- Claes!
- Yes, yes, yes.
And while the selfies hail, the originals made ready to meet their copies.
- I am afraid that it will be so similar that I get existential scams.
- Yes!
I die.
Why am I dying?
- Everyone is so nervous!
Oh my God!
Come and look!
Here you have them!
- Hey!
- Oh damn!
But but, fuck what sick!
Oh that's so damn sick!
- What is it?
So I get a scam of this.
Oh god what strange this is.
Servant, hello you!
- Damn what special!
- So I have to say ...
- I really agree.
It's damn sick.
But I'm totally wandged.
Because there are extreme similarities.
- You have birthmarks in the same places.
- It's actually totally sick.
- We have some plans tonight.
You have a sold out show here at Scala all winter.
You drive tonight.
- Yes, we would have liked you two to go up and take the evening.
- Oh, damn.
- I get shitty too.
- Say this: Servant!
My name is Billy Öhman.
- God Cursed Billy.
We will introduce ourselves first.
- Yes, of course.
I'm Billy Öhman.
And this is my brother.
- I'm Leif.
And it was somewhere where it started to get up for people that something wasn't right.
And the remaining minutes on stage, became a bit of a nightmare.
- Yes, today we will see a wonderful show!
- This is a disaster.
- What happens?
Does it work or?
- I think we would drive Småland huh?